We all worry about looking after our loved ones as they get older.
But at Quark Medical, we've developed a diverse range of compassionate,
reliable, and attentive care support humanoid workers to offer round the clock
home care as an affordable monthly subscription.
Each robot is unique whilst meeting British robot safety standards.
And if your loved one would feel more comfortable with a familiar face,
we have a variety of robots who look identical to beloved personalities.
Haven comfort for companionship
independent.
Sorry darling, taking Doty Foot after bed.
Your fortunate is just a spray and wrist.
Because I fall at your age.
I've had low blood pressure faints for whole of my life.
Well, you're lucky like Ploki and I smush your head on the corner of the coffee
table.
Our land teep for a Sunday iron door step.
I'll fall down the marble staircase.
Well, the marble staircase in my two-bed terrace.
The warm environment can be lethal.
Hey, don't joke with it.
Now, in terms of recovery.
You're going needed.
You live with anybody.
Yeah.
I live with my son Michael and should be here any minute.
Well, it's taking a long time.
Look, love.
Does my guy really exist?
Mom.
Oh, Michael, where the how have you been?
Um How did you fall?
I fainted, and apparently I'm very lucky I didn't fall in a fire or a hornet's
nest.
You can pick up our pain relief prescription at the reception.
Look on me after you.
If she's going home, I'm going home.
Mr.
Thomas!
We cannot send you horn pony on if you're won't going to assist it.
Don't belong in a care home.
I mean, look at me.
I can lift a bed.
What a box
side.
Oh I've just gotta take this.
You go through to the kitchen.
It's it's just about the uh the broadband the um the the gigabyte the um the
transponder Hello babe Yes I'm
home no I haven'told her yet she's just had a
fall delaying it's just a difficult conversation to
have that's hopeful I'm not a nappy wearing breastfed Emperor
Baby
Mum I don't like to pass stuff Yeah yeah I'm sorry I just haven't had time
to plant it I got it I know I know August sixteenth Yeah doesn't seem like
two years does it's still everywhere it's called a
David Rose that's why I chose I I will get round to it I
promise you to know that I know how
lucky I am that you're here going through this alone would just be
awful
Okay um so um I I was late picking you up because
I was with um Renee I was with
Renee She's changed she's getting therapy She's
getting therapy because she cheated on you with her karate
instructor Yes She's making real inroads with that and and it's
BJJ Brazilian Well, as long as you don't do anything stupid.
Like move back in with her.
Oh you back.
I still love her, Mum.
How can you be sure she isn't still cheating on you with her karate instructor?
She told me.
And and it's Brazilian Jiu Jitsu.
It's a lot more lethal than karate.
I'm42.
I'm not meant to be with my mum on a Saturday night watching Michael MacIntyre.
You were cackling at Michael MacIntosh jokes about buffers.
Cackling.
I'm sorry, I didn't realise you're having such a bad time.
Mum.
I can't just leave my wife and look after you the way you looked after Dad.
That is very different.
Your dad was very sick.
And I don't need looking after.
Well I'm I'm sorry.
I just have to start building my own life and stop being a
nappy wearing breastfed emperor baby.
Are you gonna eat that?
No
bits of plate in it.
Could you please make me another one,
Mom?
Shit.
Hello, dear.
I heard about your fool.
It wasn't a fool.
I fainted.
I've had low blood pressure all my life.
Look at you.
You can't even carry your tray.
Let me help you.
I don't need help.
You're injured.
There we go.
Oh, it is lucky Michael lives with you and can help.
Otherwise you would be all alone.
Yes, he's a real God's.
Because you don't have any grandkids, do you?
At least you get to spoil your one and only child.
Trudy, I ordered your toasting on wholemeal bread for your bowel
health.
Imagine needing one of those ghastly things.
I've had stories that would curl your toes.
Towning on their owners, spying on them, and um some people are doing things
with their robots that they really should not be
doing.
We are so lucky.
I mean I have my daughter, all my grandchildren and Jeffrey,
and you have Michael.
Oh my God.
What that woman over there has just grabbed her robot's
penis.
You know, Michael, if you were in a good relationship,
I'd be very happy for you.
It's a rush.
Oh no no it's nothing.
Apparently it's a totally normal side effect.
Of what?
Oh, I did some clinical trials.
It's only only five days.
Really good money, though.
Sounds dangerous.
Mom.
If it was dangerous, do you really think the drug companies would do it?
Now the whole reason I did it was because um I wanted to buy you a
present.
Now I want you to be safe And if you fall again,
I'm not gonna be here.
So you got me robot.
Hey, Michael Burman.
Take it away, please.
I don't want it.
She does want it.
Bring it in.
Well, I've already paid the
deposit.
How heavy these models are.
Okay.
Let me help.
Thank you.
That's enormously helpful.
Welcome to your Android Z58 forward slash one hundred.
Basic care model.
She's very easy to operate.
Does have a few dings and scuffs.
After all, she is pretty loved.
Pretty loved.
Second hand.
Yep.
Little more than second, but hey, that's why she's such a bargain.
This is a very popular model back in the day.
In spite of some some pretty catastrophic taping errors.
Problems that have all been resolved.
Yes.
Okay, so you've got a twenty-four month contract.
Uh your48 hour trial period begins when you switch her on.
You absolutely cannot have sex with this model.
Sure.
Finally, I'm just going to need a signature at the bottom.
Okay.
Lovely.
And can I please also just get a photo?
Yeah.
Oh no, it's not that's not a fat.
Oh.
Lovely.
Great.
Uh, well, enjoy.
U Uh, if you have any problems, uh issues,
there's a number on the back.
Uh the call center is open one till two PM on Saturday.
That's the third Saturday of every month.
Have a lovely time enjoy.
So you if you need someone to talk to.
Or she can help with shopping, cleaning.
Why couldn't I just have a car?
But a human.
It cost a fortune.
And and what what if you fall on their day off?
This is twenty-four seven.
Feeling said they spy on you.
What happens if they drain my account?
Who I don't know.
Mum this means that you can stay in your home.
I don't want it.
Look how you gonna manage, you don't even drive anymore.
Sorry.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just leaving now.
Yeah, it's arrived.
She loves it.
She's so happy.
Uh what's it look like?
Uh just a woman with enormous dead
eyes.
Though it's not better looking than you.
You're the most beautiful woman in the world.
Hello.
Babe just give it a go,
Mom.
Forty eight
hours.
Stupid
Oh hi how'd you fell haven't seen Phillips this excited since Digry Tola got a
kidney cist I I fainted You've always had low blood pressure
Sally died Sally Harris Sally Wittle Sally Harris is dying Sally Widdle
is dead Oh did you find a copper Nah I'm really
busy got time I might eat one and all my friends are dead I'm never going
to plant this rose good job you've got Michael is
moved out to the
country Ballster
this probably for the best mother Norman
Baits I guess so I just feel
alone I've been alone all my life is not that bad unless you go in a
heat wave like my uncle Nelson He was so blurry by the time they found him
he trembled his eyes and he was not sure model to start with Oh Michael got
it for me because he felt guilty about leaving Oh no
no no don't Arin on sending it back sending back
No I'm
not
Times has got a button at the back of the
head
Hello Bonjour Bonjourno Garnet Good and
hard you have chosen English now tell me your name by
saying it into my face holes I can't sound
so nice to meet you so zoo so my name is Android I'm a
Z58 forward slash one hundred robot carer but you can name me something more
memorable please say the name you'd prefer Linda
Hi so my name is now Linda my
sister's name Oh my
sister doing what is it doing What
is it doing Oh my
goding
Retinos gun complete I have uploaded your full medical profile I thought I
turned on you I'm just trying to sit via your brain Let's get back to the
shop Don't leave me alone with it I can't stay here and play with
your robot gotta get back to work text me if he starts attacking
you
I just don't want to be on my own with it it's creepy look at it
What is that oh I found it in donation what you think I see you alright.
Can't talk to you with that on your head.
Tom, you look like an idiot.
So you just got a robot.
She's terrified of it.
Oh wow.
I had no idea that androids were still being used.
I thought been forced to decommission them.
Roxy, would you like to speak to a vintage robot?
Hey.
I sure would.
Oh go on.
Hi.
I'm Roxy.
I help Tom.
Hello.
I am Linda.
I help so It is nice to meet you,
Linda.
It is nice to meet you, Roxy.
I like your top.
Thank you, Linda.
It belongs to Tom's wife.
She is dead.
It comfort him to see me wearing her clothes.
Perhaps I will see you again for incidental social interactions.
I would enjoy that.
But I am being sent back.
So, so, so thinks I am going to kill her.
Are you going to kill her, Linda?
Yes.
I'm also going to kill Tom.
I am joking.
I am also joking.
She won't hurt you.
I'm sure they've sort of all that out.
I find Roxy enormously helpful.
I can't imagine life without you, eh?
You're gonna have to go home at some point,
so I'm closing in ten minutes.
Tell Linda to stay in her own room.
If you feel uncomfortable.
Fine.
Come on, Linda.
We're going.
I'm not buying that.
He did mono slippers improve circulation.
Increase blood flow repairs ligament bone and tissue damage.
All right.
I'm not buying the
sunglasses How
much?
All right.
I don't know the value of nothing
show
danger Danger Danger.
Stop it.
You're supposed to stay in Michael's room.
Falling asleep in the bath can be lethal.
Iconic songstress Whitney Houston tragically put away.
I am naked.
Yes I can see most of your right breast and the top of your mom's pubis.
Your naked body is not a problem for me.
But it's a problem for me.
Nobody see me naked soon stain.
Here is clothing for your nakedness.
Don't discuss me.
Don't what?
You seem angry.
I will lighten the mood with humor.
Why did the donut go to the dentist?
Piss off, Linda.
Where would you like me to piss off to?
Piss off to the room I told you to stay in.
Only stay there.
I just want a quiet evening alone watching the
TV.
The donut go to the dentist.
Piss
off is all
about using your
button.
You You tripped and hit your head.
I assessed you as Cotton Cast with ligament damage in the
neck.
Nothing I remember is not enough to a tusk in a bakery.
Yes.
Lord Sugar said the failure of the task lay with Kevin.
Kevin.
It was a bully.
Kevin said it was a big mistake.
And wish them the best of luck.
But he did not sound sincere.
A trip.
Yes.
On the heated mono slipper I told you to buy.
Oh no, no fall.
I didn't fall.
I tripped over a hated mono slipper that this idiot insisted I get.
Well I'm sending her back.
I wouldn't do that.
You can't keep me here.
I have a son.
I don't live alone.
Now I know that's not true.
Because Linda explained everything about your situation when you arrive.
Stupid twat.
Mrs.
Bivin.
This stupid twat is the reason I'm discharging you.
Sorry to Linda.
Thank you very much.
Stupid.
No.
Download all your home care information on Linda.
So you can go warm.
She's doing a great
job.
The purple one is Michaels.
No, it was Would you like me to throw it away to clear?
No, no, don't touch anything.
By scanning your retina, I have measured your dopamine and endorphin level.
You are said music might improve your
mood.
Hello?
Mom, Mom, are you okay?
I just I just saw your miss.
I tripped.
Another four.
No, I tripped.
Idiot robot's fault.
She insisted on getting me a mono slipper.
Tell him.
The mono slipper was my idea.
What's a mono slipper?
And your grid will defeat him.
The mono slipper boasts a luxurious flee fabric that feels irresistibly soft and
cozy.
Does sound soft and cozy.
She put me in hospital with ligament damage on a mouth concussion.
It just sounds like an accident.
I think you weren't alone.
Mom, please consider keeping her.
What anybody on the
stone
I'm
missing.
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay.
Yeah, sure.
Okay, bye,
Mom.
Would you like to talk?
Dogg improves mental health.
You're a robot.
Yes, I am a robot.
It just seems like everything in my life has been taken
away.
Dave's gone.
Michael's love.
I've no grandkids.
Soon I lose my independent and then I'll probably lose my
marbles.
I can help you find your
I don't know how I'm going to do this last
bit.
Hello.
But what ever life I've got left.
I do not wish to spend it with a robot.
I know you don't understand.
Nobody
does.
I am fired like Kevin.
Thank you for this opportunity.
And I wish you the best of luck.
And like Kevin.
I am
sincere.
You sound like you are struggling.
Is your head stuck inside a bull?
No, I can manage on my own.
You're not being bad.
I've already seen your mom's building.
Just leave me alone,
Linda.
Start search.
How to stop feeling sad about a dead
husband.
Why are human sad when I life end?
Moving for
me.
We start such what is the meaning of a human
life.
Linda it's time.
You uh want to return your robot.
Yes, please.
Well period's for, you know.
They're not for everyone.
So so so your next dose of pain relief medication is to be taken after lunch.
Oh, thank you.
All right,
then.
How did you know that was my favorite?
You had a massive dopamine's bike when you saw them in the freezer.
This one' The old shadow box.
I hope you find happiness.
So zoo zoo.
You don't have any wet watch, do you?
It's got total over its hands.
My rose.
You miss David, and David is dead.
That is a David Rose.
They want a dead David, the owner of the Burble Rome.
That's right.
I understand.
Zo, zoo, zoo!
It was not a robot you were to be sharing the rest of your life with.
It was dead David.
Linda Step out of the box.
How long is this stay?
I've changed my mind.
Yeah, no, I've been listening.
And I guess I'm just need your signature.
And uh can I just get a
photo.
Thank you.
Did you know Jude in the home is not made from tops?